Ethan Partridge

Full-Stack Developer

Contact

ethanpart98@gmail.com • 618-841-1204 • Eldorado, IL 62930 github.com/EthanPartridge • linkedin.com/in/ethanpartridge2021/

Summary

Motivated Computer Science graduate with a year of experience in full-stack web development. I bring communication, teamwork, and leadership skills cultivated by my experience as a Lead Programmer. I have excellent attention to detail and problem solving skills due to my training, schooling, and desire to provide valuable work.

Education

B.S. in Computer Science | 3.2 GPA | Graduated May 2021 University of Southern Indiana, Evansville, IN Sigma Pi - Theta Psi Chapter Alumni

Experience

Partridge Web Solutions - Full-Stack Developer | partridgewebsolutions.com | (Nov. 2021 - Dec. 2021)

- Designed a responsive portfolio website in Figma and translated that design into a working SEO friendly full-stack application using ASP.NET Core MVC 5.
- Aggregated data from an external API via a background process.
- Utilized APIs to display data and images, send outgoing emails, and add animations to elements.
- Provided a convenient way for clients to explore my skills and contact me.

Kickit Habit Tracker - Full-Stack Developer | kickithabittracker.com | (Jul. 2021 - Sept. 2021)

- Designed, developed, and deployed a responsive full-stack web application for tracking habits using ASP.NET Core MVC 5, Bootstrap 4, Entity Framework, and Azure.
- Designed, implemented, and manipulated a database to store user inputs.
- Provided value to users looking to easily track their habits on both desktop and mobile devices.

Home Health Care - Lead Programmer | Senior Project | (Jan. 2021 - May 2021)

- Worked with team members to develop an at-home screening website for diseases using WordPress that resulted in client satisfaction and praise.
- Discussed project requirements with the client and determined feasibility of those requirements.
- Managed programming related tasks and distributed them amongst myself and team members to ensure project completion.

Skills

- C# | ASP.NET Core MVC | Visual Studio 2019 | Microsoft Azure | Windows
- JavaScript | jQuery | HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap 4 | Figma
- SQL | Microsoft SQL Management Studio 18 | Entity Framework
- Git | GitHub